http://www.wallwords.com/privacy.asp

Login DetailsEmailPasswordRemember login on this computer?New Account*Full Name*Email*PasswordAllow Promotional Emails(We will never divulge your email to a 3rd party)
Not logged in
» Login
View Cart (0)
Your shopping cart is currently empty  Close
VOTE ·
GIFT CERTIFICATES ·
CLIENT LOGIN ·
ORDER STATUS ·
CONTACT US
HOME
Vinyl Decals
America
Misc.
Poets Corner
Business
International Quotes
Nursery
Cowboys and Cowgirls!
Sorority Wall Words
Simple Wisdom Quotes
7 Words Deal
All Categories
Design Your Own
Custom Text Designer tool
Custom Design Request Form
Upload Your Files
Advanced Search
Privacy PolicyWall Words publishes this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.wallwords.comWall Words believes that strong electronic privacy is crucial to the continuing success of the Internet as a means of communication, a commercial vehicle, and an entertainment medium. To this end, unless you designate otherwise, the information you enter here will be strictly kept between you and Wall Words.We pledge that Wall Words will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent - period.We use an order form for customers to purchase our products. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their address and zip code). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the customer if necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products.You can decide to discontinue Wall Words information and communications at any time. This site contains links to other sites. Wall Words is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their Privacy Policy may differ from ours.Use of e-mail addresses:After signing up with Wall Words, clients may receive an occasional Wall Words electronic newsletter. These e-mail addresses and other collected information are never given, sold or passed along to any third party.Your privacy is assured.
Our Products
Vinyl Decals
» Designer Decals
» » Cabin Decals
» » Farm and Garden Decals
» » Kitchen Decals
» » Laundry Decals
» » Loving Decals
» Word Clouds
» Catalog (PDF)
» African Animals
» Aliens, Planets and Stars
» Big Faces
» Digital Fish & Tropical Creatures
» Food & Kitchen Items
» Classic Cars and Vintage Vehicles
» Decorative Art
» » Angels
» Nursery
» Cowboys and Cowgirls!
» Sorority Wall Words
» Definitions
Gift Certificates
Filter By...
Sort Order
Please Select...
Sort AlphabeticallyAlphabetically (Desc.)Sort by Product IDProduct ID (Desc.)Sort By SKUSort By SKU (Desc.)Sort Price (Asc.)Sort Price (Desc.)Database OrderProduct OrderProduct Order (Desc.)Average Rating View # Products on Page
15 Per Page30 Per Page45 Per Page60 Per Page75 Per Page Filter By Keyword
»
© Copyright 2019 - Shopping cart by Visualnet Media, Inc.
